export default [
    {
      question: "What is Jaiden Animations's surname?",
      choice1: "Carter",
      choice2: "Frank",
      choice3: "Rallison",
      choice4: "Dittfach",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Where was Jaiden Animations born?",
      choice1: "Arizona, USA",
      choice2: "California, USA",
      choice3: "New York, USA",
      choice4: "Texas, USA",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "When did Jaiden Animations create her YouTube channel?",
      choice1: "5th May 2014",
      choice2: "14th August 2016",
      choice3: "17th Feburary 2014",
      choice4: "30th August 2014",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "What is Jaiden Animations song called?",
      choice1: "Life is Fun",
      choice2: "Empty",
      choice3: "Passionate Sleep",
      choice4: "Life is Empty",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Who did Jaiden Animations collaborate with to make her song?",
      choice1: "Boyinaband",
      choice2: "RoomieOfficial",
      choice3: "TwoSetViolin",
      choice4: "Davie504",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many songs has Jaiden Animations made?",
      choice1: "3",
      choice2: "1",
      choice3: "5",
      choice4: "2",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Jaiden Animations started making Animations for which Famous YouTuber's channel?", 
      choice1: "QTCindrella",
      choice2: "Ludwig",
      choice3: "iHasCupquake",
      choice4: "Dream",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which year was Jaiden Animations born?",
      choice1: "1997",
      choice2: "1999",
      choice3: "1995",
      choice4: "2005",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Jaiden Animations's favourite colour?",
        choice1: "Blue",
        choice2: "Green",
        choice3: "Red",
        choice4: "Purple",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What colour does Jaiden Animations hate?",
        choice1: "Red",
        choice2: "Green",
        choice3: "Black",
        choice4: "Orange",
        answer: 2,
    },
  ];
  